Subtitle Provide by dramacool.asia Translator [Admin.@YNG]
تم توفير الترجمة بواسطة مترجم dramacool.asia [Admin.@YNG]
♪I've been searching for the past♪
♪لقد كنت أبحث عن الماضي♪
♪This world and the face that looks like yours♪
♪هذا العالم والوجه الذي يشبه وجهك♪
♪When I start to write♪
♪عندما أبدأ الكتابة♪
♪I realize I'm slowly walking into danger♪
♪أدرك أنني أسير ببطء نحو الخطر♪
♪I thought it was destined loneliness♪
♪اعتقدت أنها كانت الوحدة المقدرة♪
♪Through lifetimes of pain, the memory stays clear♪
♪على مر العصور من الألم، تبقى الذكرى واضحة♪
♪You again and again, me step by step♪
♪أنت مرارا وتكرارا، وأنا خطوة بخطوة♪
♪Lost on the road searching for you♪
♪ضائع على الطريق أبحث عنك♪
=A Fleeting Dream=
=حلم عابر=
=Episode 4=
=الحلقة 4=
Are your hands okay?
هل يديك بخير؟
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
You have to...
عليك أن...
Youmeng.
يومينج.
(Pei Residence)
(مسكن بي)
So cool.
رائع جداً.
So comfortable.
مريح للغاية.
(Jin Se, Lian Xinruo's assistant)
(جين سي، مساعد ليان شينرو)
Awake?
مستيقظ؟
Yes, I'll go wash my face.
نعم سأذهب لأغسل وجهي.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Nothing.
لا شئ.
What's going on?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
Did the wound split open?
هل انفتح الجرح؟
No.
لا.
It was me. I just tried to shave
كنت أنا. حاولت فقط الحلاقة
and accidentally hurt my hand.
وأذيت يدي عن طريق الخطأ.
Since you took care of me so well last night,
منذ أن اعتنيت بي جيدًا الليلة الماضية،
I'll help you. Let's go.
سأساعدك. هيا بنا.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
I'll do it myself.
سأفعل ذلك بنفسي.
Don't move.
.لا تتحرك
If such a beautiful face got scratched,
إذا تم خدش مثل هذا الوجه الجميل،
I would be irresponsible.
سوف أكون غير مسؤول.
Second Master.
المعلم الثاني.
Second Master, I'm back.
سيدي الثاني، لقد عدت.
(Wen Yuan, Pei Yuze's assistant) I've already caught the person
(وين يوان، مساعد باي يوزي) لقد ألقي القبض على الشخص بالفعل
who attacked Miss Du.
الذين هاجموا الآنسة دو.
It was ordered by Lian Xinya, I'm done.
لقد تم طلبه من قبل ليان شينيا، لقد انتهيت.
Also, Lian family will elect a new family head tomorrow.
كما ستنتخب عائلة ليان غدًا رئيسًا جديدًا للعائلة.
I'm really done now.
لقد انتهيت الآن حقًا.
I didn't expect things to develop so fast.
لم أتوقع أن تتطور الأمور بهذه السرعة.
Luckily, Jin Se got the seal in advance.
لحسن الحظ، حصل جين سي على الختم مسبقًا.
Tomorrow,
غداً،
I can return to the Lian family as Lian Xinruo,
أستطيع العودة إلى عائلة ليان كـ ليان شينرو،
and become the new family head of the Lian family.
ويصبح رئيس العائلة الجديد لعائلة ليان.
For Lian Xinya to call the stewards so quickly,
لكي تقوم ليان شينيا باستدعاء المضيفين بهذه السرعة،
there must be backing.
يجب أن يكون هناك دعم.
Don't act rashly.
لا تتصرف بتهور.
The Lian family stewards are all my father's elders.
جميع أفراد عائلة ليان هم شيوخ والدي.
If they know I'm alive,
إذا علموا أنني على قيد الحياة،
they will surely support me.
إنهم سيدعمونني بالتأكيد.
Uncles and elders,
الأعمام والشيوخ،
my Father is bedridden now.
والدي طريح الفراش الآن.
The Lian family cannot be without a head even for a day.
لا يمكن لعائلة ليان أن تبقى بلا رأس حتى ليوم واحد.
That's why I invited you all today
لهذا السبب دعوتكم جميعا اليوم
to discuss the head of the Lian family.
لمناقشة رئيس عائلة ليان.
Ever since Mr. Lian had an accident,
منذ أن تعرض السيد ليان لحادث،
Xinya has handled everything thoroughly.
لقد تعاملت شينيا مع كل شيء بدقة.
Everyone has seen it.
لقد رأى الجميع ذلك.
So the candidate for the head of Lian family
لذا فإن المرشح لمنصب رئيس عائلة ليان
must be Xinya.
يجب أن تكون شينيا.
Thank you, Uncle Pei.
شكرا لك عمي باي.
(If you ask me, who holds the Lian family seal)
(إذا سألتني، من يحمل ختم عائلة ليان)
(should be the head of the Lian family.)
(يجب أن يكون رئيسًا لعائلة ليان.)
(Isn't it relying on Pei Yujie behind the scenes?)
(أليس هذا الاعتماد على باي يوجي خلف الكواليس؟)
(I think the Lian family will soon change to Pei.)
(أعتقد أن عائلة ليان ستتغير قريبًا إلى باي.)
(I wish the family head were here.)
(أتمنى أن يكون رب الأسرة هنا.)
Since everyone has no objection,
وبما أن الجميع ليس لديهم اعتراض،
then the candidate for Lian family head is...
إذن المرشح لرئاسة عائلة ليان هو...
Wait.
انتظر.
This is... Isn't this...
هذا... أليس هذا...
Sorry, I'm late.
آسف، لقد تأخرت.
Isn't this Miss Xinruo?
أليست هذه الآنسة شينرو؟
You're not dead, great!
أنت لست ميتًا، رائع!
Du Youmeng,
دو يومينج,
why are you here?
لماذا انت هنا؟
Today the Lian family is choosing a new head,
اليوم تختار عائلة ليان رئيسًا جديدًا،
of course I have to come back.
بالطبع يجب علي أن أعود.
You're not even a Lian family member,
أنت لست حتى عضوًا في عائلة ليان،
what right do you have to choose the family head?
ما هو الحق الذي لديك في اختيار رب الأسرة؟
Xinya.
شينيا.
You don't know whether I'm a Lian family member?
ألا تعلم أنني عضو في عائلة ليان؟
I am Lian Xinruo.
أنا ليان شينرو.
You...
أنت...
I brought back the Lian family seal.
لقد أحضرت ختم عائلة ليان.
How is this possible?
كيف هذا ممكن؟
Impossible.
مستحيل.
Really?
حقًا؟
Yes, it really is the Lian family seal.
نعم، إنه حقا ختم عائلة ليان.
Impossible.
مستحيل.
The Lian family seal disappeared five years ago.
اختفى ختم عائلة ليان منذ خمس سنوات.
This must be fake.
لابد أن يكون هذا مزيفًا.
Great, Xinruo.
عظيم ، شينرو.
You're finally back.
لقد عدت أخيرا.
This seal is real,
هذا الختم حقيقي
but the person may not be.
ولكن الشخص قد لا يكون كذلك.
Stewards.
الوكلاء.
Today's situation is sudden.
الوضع اليوم مفاجئ.
The election of family head is very important,
إن انتخاب رئيس العائلة أمر في غاية الأهمية،
but Miss Du cannot prove her identity,
لكن الآنسة دو لا تستطيع إثبات هويتها،
then we will discuss it another day.
ثم سنناقش هذا الأمر في يوم آخر.
Discuss another day.
ناقش في يوم آخر.
Steward.
الوكيل.
Du Youmeng.
دو يومينج.
(Pei Residence)
(مسكن بي)
Maybe you're right.
ربما كنت على حق.
I thought reclaiming the Lian family would be too simple.
اعتقدت أن استعادة عائلة ليان سيكون أمرًا بسيطًا للغاية.
Don't rush.
لا تستعجل.
After all, Pei Yujie has operated in Hu City for so many years.
بعد كل شيء، عملت Pei Yujie في مدينة Hu لسنوات عديدة.
The Lian family has long been infiltrated by his influence.
لقد كانت عائلة ليان مخترقة منذ فترة طويلة بتأثيره.
The Lian father and daughter
الأب وابنته ليان
are nothing but his puppets.
ليسوا سوى دمى في يده.
I know.
أنا أعرف.
But now all the Lian family stewards
ولكن الآن جميع أفراد عائلة ليان
dare not oppose Pei Yujie openly.
لا تجرؤ على معارضة باي يوجي علانية.
I'm worried that if this continues,
أنا قلق من أنه إذا استمر هذا،
the foundation of the Lian family will be completely exhausted.
سيتم استنفاد أساس عائلة ليان بالكامل.
Compared to the position of family head,
بالمقارنة مع منصب رب الأسرة،
there's an even more serious matter now.
هناك مسألة أكثر خطورة الآن.
I suspect your Father's death is related to Pei Yujie.
أظن أن موت والدك مرتبط ببي يوجي.
What?
ماذا؟
Back then, everything was done flawlessly.
في ذلك الوقت، كان كل شيء يتم دون أخطاء.
The person behind it was not simple.
الشخص الذي كان وراء ذلك لم يكن بسيطا.
Looking at the current state of the Lian family,
بالنظر إلى الحالة الحالية لعائلة ليان،
this possibility is very high.
هذا الاحتمال مرتفع جدًا.
So you must be careful.
لذلك يجب عليك أن تكون حذرا.
Yao, what do you think?
ياو ماذا تعتقد؟
Godfather, Du Youmeng's words cannot be trusted.
العراب، لا يمكن الوثوق بكلام دو يومينغ.
You grew up with Lian Xinruo,
لقد نشأت مع ليان شينرو،
you know best what is true and false.
أنت تعرف ما هو الصحيح وما هو الخطأ.
Have someone keep an eye on Du Youmeng and Pei Yuze.
اطلب من شخص ما أن يراقب Du Youmeng وPei Yuze.
Report to me immediately if anything unusual happens.
أبلغني على الفور إذا حدث أي شيء غير عادي.
Understood.
مفهومة.
Go confirm again
اذهب للتأكيد مرة أخرى
whether Lian Xinruo really died.
هل ماتت ليان شينرو حقا؟
Since you brought up the old matters of the Lian family,
وبما أنك أثرت الأمور القديمة لعائلة ليان،
then whether you are Lian Xinruo or not,
إذن سواء كنت ليان شينرو أم لا،
you cannot stay.
لا يمكنك البقاء.
Hurry up, you all.
عجلوا جميعا.
Miss, we've dug it up.
آنسة، لقد حفرنا ذلك.
You brat.
يا ولدي.
How dare you lie to me.
كيف تجرؤ على الكذب علي؟
Fine, dig out the body.
حسنًا، استخرج الجثة.
Yes.
نعم.
Du Youmeng, what are you doing? Let me go!
دو يومينغ، ماذا تفعل؟ دعني أذهب!
Didn't you follow me all the way
ألم تتبعني طوال الطريق؟
to kill me?
لتقتلني؟
Why ask me instead?
لماذا تسألني بدلا من ذلك؟
Stop pretending.
توقف عن التظاهر.
You are not Lian Xinruo at all.
أنت لست ليان شينرو على الإطلاق.
Really? I remember at the Lian Residence,
حقاً؟ أتذكر في ليان ريزيدنس،
the first time you saw me,
المرة الأولى التي رأيتني فيها،
you called me Xinruo.
لقد ناديتني بـ شينرو.
You're not Lian Xinruo,
أنت لست ليان شينرو،
who exactly are you?
من أنت بالضبط؟
Let me tell you.
دعني أخبرك.
Even if the Lian family is given to you,
حتى لو أعطيت لك عائلة ليان،
you won't be able to hold it.
لن تتمكن من الاحتفاظ بها.
I'll kill you!
سأقتلك!
Good luck.
حظ سعيد.
(Such skills, definitely not Xinruo.)
(مثل هذه المهارات، بالتأكيد ليست Xinruo.)
Yao.
لهم.
Why are you here, Miss Du?
لماذا أنت هنا يا آنسة دو؟
Weren't you following me all along?
ألم تكن تتبعني طوال الوقت؟
You are really sharp.
أنت ذكي حقا.
What? You still doesn't believe I am Lian Xinruo?
ماذا؟ مازلت لا تصدق أنني ليان شينرو؟
Well, I've turned into this now.
حسنًا، لقد تحولت إلى هذا الآن.
It's normal if you don't believe me.
من الطبيعي أن لا تصدقني.
A few days ago, I questioned you thoroughly,
قبل أيام قليلة، سألتك سؤالاً دقيقاً،
and you wouldn't admit it.
ولن تعترف بذلك.
Why now suddenly reveal your identity?
لماذا الآن تكشف عن هويتك فجأة؟
My Father did such a wrong thing,
لقد فعل والدي مثل هذا الشيء الخاطئ،
how could I admit it?
كيف يمكنني أن أعترف بذلك؟
But now, seeing the Lian family like this,
ولكن الآن، رؤية عائلة ليان على هذا النحو،
I have to return.
يجب علي أن أعود.
I cannot watch the Lian family fall by my hands.
لا أستطيع أن أرى عائلة ليان تسقط بين يدي.
You must have suffered a lot over these years.
لا بد أنك عانيت كثيرًا خلال هذه السنوات.
Whether it was hard or not, it's all past now.
سواء كان الأمر صعبًا أم لا، فقد أصبح كل شيء في الماضي الآن.
Yao, I must reclaim the Lian family now.
ياو، يجب عليّ استعادة عائلة ليان الآن.
For the sake of our past bond,
من أجل رابطتنا الماضية،
Yao, please help me.
ياو، من فضلك ساعدني.
Okay.
تمام.
But you have to tell me honestly,
ولكن عليك أن تخبرني بصراحة،
what your relationship with Pei Yuze really is?
ما هي علاقتك الحقيقية مع باي يوزي؟
♪The city night silently envelops♪
♪ليلة المدينة تغلف بصمت♪
♪Hate and love♪
♪الكراهية والحب♪
♪His voice lingers by my ear♪
♪صوته يبقى في أذني♪
♪In this unavoidable dead end I encounter♪
♪في هذا الطريق المسدود الذي لا مفر منه الذي أواجهه♪
♪How can wounded love burn again♪
♪كيف يمكن للحب الجريح أن يحترق مرة أخرى♪
♪Leaving only his unpredictable smile♪
♪لم يبق منه سوى ابتسامته غير المتوقعة♪
♪My heart receives his gentle signals drop by drop♪
♪يستقبل قلبي إشاراته اللطيفة قطرة قطرة♪
♪Wounded wings try to rely on♪
♪الأجنحة الجريحة تحاول الاعتماد على♪
♪Secret love♪
♪الحب السري♪
♪Hidden in his most passionate embrace♪
♪مختبئ في أحضانه الأكثر شغفًا♪
♪Ignoring the noisy lights and wine♪
♪ تجاهل الأضواء الصاخبة والنبيذ ♪
♪Being a quiet cat in his arms♪
♪أكون قطة هادئة بين ذراعيه♪
♪Entwining the rest of my life, with no escape♪
♪تشابك بقية حياتي، بلا مفر♪